omiga-plus.com 2018-06-16

# Omiga Plus - Your tool for a clean desktop

Collection and Use of Information

Omiga Plus does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail, age, gender, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information"). 

Omiga Plus may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are on Omiga Plus's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout as well as for other customer service purposes. Omiga Plus's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information.

Omiga Plus may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. Omiga Plus collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. Omiga Plus will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users.

Sharing and Disclosure of Information

Omiga Plus does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. Omiga Plus may disclose your Personal Information if Omiga Plus believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Omiga Plus (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Omiga Plus (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Omiga Plus services or members of the public.

Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the Omiga Plus website and software and must LEAVE immediately.

Explicit Content

You understand that by using the Service, you may encounter content that may be deemed offensive, indecent, or objectionable, which content may or may not be identified as having explicit language. Nevertheless, you agree to use the Site at your sole risk and that Omiga Plus shall have no liability to you for content that may be found to be offensive, indecent, or objectionable. Omiga Plus shall have no liability or responsibility to you for any content or materials that may be available in connection with the Site that you might find objectionable.

Security

Omiga Plus takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although Omiga Plus cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, Omiga Plus has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.

Changes to Policy

From time to time, Omiga Plus may revise this Policy. Omiga Plus will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information Omiga Plus collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed.

Change or Removal of Information

If a user's e-mail address changes or you wish you remove your e-mail address, you can contact us at: omigaplus-client@gmail.com with the request or by contacting us at the contact information listed below.
